[{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9864"},"rt":18706,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52130,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9865"},"rt":8921,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":61153,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9866"},"rt":26058,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":87314,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9867"},"rt":27080,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":114494,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9868"},"rt":52121,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166717,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d986a"},"rt":7703,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":177550,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d986b"},"rt":22734,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200383,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d986c"},"rt":66191,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266684,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d986d"},"rt":32765,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":300114,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d986e"},"rt":26596,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326814,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d986f"},"rt":11985,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338896,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9870"},"rt":3604,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342605,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9871"},"rt":17083,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359787,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9872"},"rt":23931,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383817,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"403 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9873"},"rt":44042,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427975,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9884"},"rt":28246,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":307877,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9885"},"rt":18503,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326500,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D 11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9886"},"rt":8434,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":335042,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"5C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9887"},"rt":8991,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":344139,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9888"},"rt":19224,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":363472,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I 03 PMI I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d988a"},"rt":16876,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388681,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AM11 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d988b"},"rt":25769,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414558,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F O O O X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d988c"},"rt":57334,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472002,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F X 03 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d988d"},"rt":76266,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":548384,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J J I J J J E B B B B 02 PM09 AME B B B F F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d988e"},"rt":10222,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558913,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"402 PMF E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d988f"},"rt":7457,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":566483,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9890"},"rt":10288,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":576876,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G F B 10 AMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9891"},"rt":9617,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":586617,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z Z Z E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9892"},"rt":9415,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":596143,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"303 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9893"},"rt":10026,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":606278,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98a4"},"rt":6692,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":41044,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98a5"},"rt":11759,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52977,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C 09 AM11 AMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98a6"},"rt":15598,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":68720,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98a7"},"rt":11765,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":80592,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"09 AMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98a8"},"rt":18860,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99604,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"4O O I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98aa"},"rt":7850,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":114596,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ab"},"rt":21205,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135960,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C M 01 PM01 PMX X X X C B F B N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ac"},"rt":43869,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179999,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"F B X M J D 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ad"},"rt":15439,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":195601,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ae"},"rt":8426,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204188,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98af"},"rt":9453,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213806,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98b0"},"rt":7641,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221609,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98b1"},"rt":13739,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":235505,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B N Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98b2"},"rt":7857,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243514,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98b3"},"rt":9778,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253448,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"3J X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98c4"},"rt":61135,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":168196,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AMA 11 AMA A O O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98c5"},"rt":27809,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196326,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98c6"},"rt":29509,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":225961,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C C 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98c7"},"rt":34133,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":260207,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"U U U F F F F G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98c8"},"rt":14120,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":274437,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ca"},"rt":9630,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":289634,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98cb"},"rt":21451,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311194,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98cc"},"rt":28762,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340066,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98cd"},"rt":10994,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":351169,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ce"},"rt":105596,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456875,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C B F Z M F Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98cf"},"rt":9754,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466933,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98d0"},"rt":6276,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473321,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98d1"},"rt":17363,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490798,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98d2"},"rt":43515,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534425,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PMO 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98d3"},"rt":16108,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550645,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98e4"},"rt":105075,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":281175,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A H 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98e5"},"rt":40470,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":322110,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"U U 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98e6"},"rt":10697,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":332971,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C 12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98e7"},"rt":11788,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":344919,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98e8"},"rt":106120,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":451186,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I 11 AM11 AMO O A H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ea"},"rt":48095,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":510058,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM09 AMJ J J B B O O X C C G E E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98eb"},"rt":61246,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":571405,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"5F F B I F F F X O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ec"},"rt":61667,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":633395,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"B B B B 12 PMB 03 PMO 04 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ed"},"rt":19988,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":653724,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"G G J 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ee"},"rt":13785,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":667667,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PMF 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98ef"},"rt":11735,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679564,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98f0"},"rt":9508,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":689223,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98f1"},"rt":16544,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":705914,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M Z 02 PMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98f2"},"rt":9689,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":715755,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d98f3"},"rt":36740,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":752657,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X X X K X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9904"},"rt":13045,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66601,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9905"},"rt":9786,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76502,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K U G D E 04 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9906"},"rt":40624,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117235,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"C C C C A A A A Z C A A A C C A A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9907"},"rt":29013,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146364,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9908"},"rt":17116,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":163604,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O I I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d990a"},"rt":9256,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":174934,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d990b"},"rt":38442,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213491,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"J I C H H C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d990c"},"rt":41859,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255473,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"9C X X B B I J G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d990d"},"rt":16888,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":272479,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5B B J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d990e"},"rt":7151,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279744,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d990f"},"rt":11635,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291501,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9910"},"rt":7111,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298737,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9911"},"rt":56630,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":355487,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9912"},"rt":24983,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380592,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PMO O 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9913"},"rt":49390,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430106,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,J,N,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PMC C C M M X X M C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9924"},"rt":17502,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77512,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9925"},"rt":16376,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":93996,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3A K I F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9926"},"rt":6892,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100986,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9927"},"rt":50172,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151256,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,K","hovered":"02 PM01 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9928"},"rt":16890,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":168343,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d992a"},"rt":46975,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":221496,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d992b"},"rt":116209,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337804,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d992c"},"rt":55352,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393786,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d992d"},"rt":22067,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":415955,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d992e"},"rt":7223,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423283,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d992f"},"rt":20877,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444258,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9930"},"rt":56072,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500437,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9931"},"rt":72771,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":573313,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9932"},"rt":15061,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":588730,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9933"},"rt":14573,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603399,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9944"},"rt":28383,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130015,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM08 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9945"},"rt":21853,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152102,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"D D G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9946"},"rt":55635,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208000,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9947"},"rt":17764,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226042,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"06 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9948"},"rt":51313,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":277613,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I I 03 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d994a"},"rt":86118,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":369147,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d994b"},"rt":54983,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424541,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d994c"},"rt":111957,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":536710,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,G,P","hovered":"12 PM4J J 11 AMJ A A 0I E E E E E J J A A A F G G G 10 AM10 AMB B F F B B C C C E C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d994d"},"rt":35099,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":572347,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d994e"},"rt":24066,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":596685,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B M 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d994f"},"rt":28466,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":625356,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,L,M","hovered":"10 AM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9950"},"rt":30533,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":656082,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9951"},"rt":12111,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":668549,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9952"},"rt":12064,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":680837,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PMX X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9953"},"rt":39600,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720598,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9964"},"rt":46314,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204668,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A A 10 AM11 AMF F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9965"},"rt":10820,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":215612,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9966"},"rt":20121,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":235867,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C 09 AMC C C C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9967"},"rt":120613,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":356574,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F F F K K K 12 PMK K K F F F 11 AMK K K F 09 AM10 AMA A H H I C J H H K F F K K 01 PM01 PMU B D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9968"},"rt":201729,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":558583,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"I O A F 7O O O C C C I O A H A 10 AMC C 09 AMC C A A H K I I 2C 09 AMC C 11 AMG I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d996a"},"rt":11620,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":577884,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d996b"},"rt":44213,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622194,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J J I I C H F X X O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d996c"},"rt":139754,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":762046,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"B X X O A A A G G G G G G F F F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d996d"},"rt":31025,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":793697,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J I I I 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d996e"},"rt":87640,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":881540,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F J J J J J E E E E B B 11 AM12 PM01 PMM B B E 02 PM02 PMX X X C C C O O O O O O Z Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d996f"},"rt":10669,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892540,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9970"},"rt":6744,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":899850,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9971"},"rt":38994,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":938945,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AM12 PMZ 504 PMN Z I I I J A F B F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9972"},"rt":63375,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1002413,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM03 PMI I I I I I I I E E E J J F B B M G C C X X X X X X X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9973"},"rt":221696,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1224396,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.416666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,K","hovered":"I J J F F B B M M M 12 PMM M C C C O O A A A E E J J B B F G G G F F F G C C C O M M B B B F G F F F F F G A A K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9984"},"rt":61510,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166231,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMO 11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9985"},"rt":7718,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":174331,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"1K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9986"},"rt":12057,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186484,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM11 AMF C C 11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9987"},"rt":7266,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":193849,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9988"},"rt":16521,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210466,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d998a"},"rt":7554,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229283,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d998b"},"rt":33785,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263165,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"3F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d998c"},"rt":44945,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308216,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C B B B 708 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d998d"},"rt":36724,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":345038,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d998e"},"rt":29513,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374651,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J 02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d998f"},"rt":12626,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387384,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"302 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9990"},"rt":15208,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402688,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9991"},"rt":20428,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423213,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9992"},"rt":13577,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436889,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9993"},"rt":20648,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457717,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99a4"},"rt":12835,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302811,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99a5"},"rt":11399,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":314332,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99a6"},"rt":11624,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326067,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99a7"},"rt":17229,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":343627,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99a8"},"rt":19373,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":363095,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99aa"},"rt":2547,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":367625,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ab"},"rt":2028,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369752,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ac"},"rt":1442,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371293,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ad"},"rt":2449,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":373904,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ae"},"rt":1421,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375461,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99af"},"rt":230,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375895,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99b0"},"rt":2057,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378095,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99b1"},"rt":1847,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":380055,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99b2"},"rt":1483,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381750,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99b3"},"rt":1396,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383340,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99c4"},"rt":57080,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129459,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99c5"},"rt":37488,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167058,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"8H D H H H D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99c6"},"rt":32128,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199294,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99c7"},"rt":65784,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":265199,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99c8"},"rt":28997,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":294508,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ca"},"rt":32722,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":333024,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"989A A E E E G G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99cb"},"rt":54473,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387600,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99cc"},"rt":29067,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416772,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99cd"},"rt":14857,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":431729,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ce"},"rt":18601,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":450435,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99cf"},"rt":12606,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463142,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99d0"},"rt":4812,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468059,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99d1"},"rt":30530,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498686,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"M O Z C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99d2"},"rt":22603,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521391,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"Z H 03 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99d3"},"rt":60282,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":581780,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,I","hovered":"M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99e4"},"rt":23583,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77625,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"3O 11 AMF A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99e5"},"rt":6086,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83838,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99e6"},"rt":22599,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106561,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A 01 PM12 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99e7"},"rt":48797,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155483,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PMB O 05 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99e8"},"rt":170420,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326021,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I G G 01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AMI I I I 02 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ea"},"rt":6277,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335478,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99eb"},"rt":68011,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403599,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"4O O X X B B B B F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ec"},"rt":24107,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427981,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G B B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ed"},"rt":36615,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":464701,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ee"},"rt":8390,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473207,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99ef"},"rt":7803,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481134,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM01 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99f0"},"rt":9960,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491218,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"L L F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99f1"},"rt":15230,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506570,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"P Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99f2"},"rt":11604,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":518300,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d99f3"},"rt":13957,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":532351,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"B 03 PM02 PM02 PMX X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a04"},"rt":8621,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77324,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a05"},"rt":9206,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86707,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM10 AM12 PME E D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a06"},"rt":9595,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96507,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a07"},"rt":28364,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124974,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"104 PM04 PMU U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a08"},"rt":33513,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158576,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a0a"},"rt":8602,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":173741,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a0b"},"rt":11033,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184957,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a0c"},"rt":26242,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211290,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a0d"},"rt":17852,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229257,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a0e"},"rt":7073,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236493,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a0f"},"rt":8744,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245345,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a10"},"rt":4555,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249996,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a11"},"rt":5272,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":255363,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a12"},"rt":1950,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257413,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a13"},"rt":7381,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264897,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a24"},"rt":11209,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":48720,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a25"},"rt":9525,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58359,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F 01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a26"},"rt":28030,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86495,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":8,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,O,I,J,H,F,K,E,G","hovered":"C A A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a27"},"rt":5818,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92423,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a28"},"rt":7393,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99923,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a2a"},"rt":8056,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":110005,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a2b"},"rt":2768,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112878,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a2c"},"rt":698,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113685,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a2d"},"rt":638,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":114429,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a2e"},"rt":628,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115167,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a2f"},"rt":551,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115845,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a30"},"rt":1434,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117413,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a31"},"rt":593,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":118150,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a32"},"rt":583,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118843,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a33"},"rt":4045,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122998,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a44"},"rt":46571,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124471,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a45"},"rt":13487,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138060,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D 8D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a46"},"rt":36850,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":175011,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"Z C C C C C C 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a47"},"rt":16101,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191214,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,B","hovered":"F 04 PM04 PM04 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a48"},"rt":36092,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227614,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.833333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F,G","hovered":"U U I I I 12 PMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a4a"},"rt":9013,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":241617,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a4b"},"rt":49908,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291625,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,O,X","hovered":"I I M J J J O O O X X X O O O O X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a4c"},"rt":126887,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418610,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.16666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"B B B M B L B I I I J C O H H B B 12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMB B B B B B 01 PMM M B B E F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a4d"},"rt":23319,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442194,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a4e"},"rt":25308,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467593,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F F G F F F Z O B B F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a4f"},"rt":13135,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480893,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a50"},"rt":10211,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491205,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"8F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a51"},"rt":41418,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":532720,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"7Z N N Z Z L H H H H H L P Z Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a52"},"rt":10507,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543324,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a53"},"rt":17997,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561423,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"Z Z 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a64"},"rt":47798,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115005,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM01 PMX X 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a65"},"rt":16193,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131300,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a66"},"rt":7798,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139197,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a67"},"rt":63877,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203164,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMU U 04 PM04 PMU U 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a68"},"rt":42596,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246012,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O I O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMU U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a6a"},"rt":9923,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":258831,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a6b"},"rt":12193,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271116,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a6c"},"rt":54907,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326116,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B L 6E I J J J X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a6d"},"rt":22830,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":349036,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O B B 12 PM12 PMJ J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a6e"},"rt":57196,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406324,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B Z Z F X X X I X F F F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a6f"},"rt":6284,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412701,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a70"},"rt":3234,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416132,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a71"},"rt":9797,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":426021,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a72"},"rt":19381,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445492,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PM03 PMB B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a73"},"rt":9425,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":455012,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a84"},"rt":12970,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105744,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2C A Z Z 01 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a85"},"rt":16968,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122810,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C Z K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a86"},"rt":16108,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139013,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A A C C 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a87"},"rt":23599,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162701,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a88"},"rt":190377,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":353167,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C U F F Z 12 PMA A O 12 PM12 PM12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a8a"},"rt":14717,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":376586,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a8b"},"rt":26014,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402687,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"2B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a8c"},"rt":42277,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445053,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H 04 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a8d"},"rt":39115,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":484255,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J X M 10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a8e"},"rt":29504,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":513852,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F 03 PM04 PMM X X M 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a8f"},"rt":10323,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524269,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a90"},"rt":7965,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":532323,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a91"},"rt":40535,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":572968,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMM 01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a92"},"rt":34420,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607480,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3X 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM10 AM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9a93"},"rt":32173,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":639742,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aa4"},"rt":12789,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":81619,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA A 1C C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aa5"},"rt":7196,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88935,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H D D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aa6"},"rt":9276,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":98317,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aa7"},"rt":6729,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105144,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aa8"},"rt":15001,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120256,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O K I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aaa"},"rt":27834,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":152914,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I G E 6E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aab"},"rt":24384,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177405,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aac"},"rt":32909,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210422,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8F F F B B B E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aad"},"rt":13886,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224610,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aae"},"rt":28688,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253402,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"G G F B B B F F F X X X M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aaf"},"rt":7035,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260541,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ab0"},"rt":17888,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278525,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B B B B F F 5F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ab1"},"rt":20624,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299248,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M C H H Z Z Z Z Z Z X F O X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ab2"},"rt":8281,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307629,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ab3"},"rt":53766,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361496,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M M M M B B B B F F G F E I 03 PM02 PMO G G F F F F B 12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ac4"},"rt":51312,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132900,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F C F F O F A 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ac5"},"rt":38319,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":171331,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A F 12 PMZ D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ac6"},"rt":28028,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199470,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,H","hovered":"008 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ac7"},"rt":20705,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":220301,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"H 04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ac8"},"rt":81650,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302064,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I,X,C,J,A,H,F,K,D,U,E,Z","hovered":"F I 12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aca"},"rt":9185,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":318246,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9acb"},"rt":27665,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346024,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"B X O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9acc"},"rt":54573,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":400712,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,G","hovered":"B B G G B B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9acd"},"rt":44948,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":445769,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"N B B 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ace"},"rt":26573,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472451,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H H C G B F 02 PM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9acf"},"rt":9671,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482233,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ad0"},"rt":9344,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491686,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ad1"},"rt":14207,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506008,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ad2"},"rt":10140,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":516257,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ad3"},"rt":17157,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":533525,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ae4"},"rt":38809,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109054,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ae5"},"rt":10647,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119809,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ae6"},"rt":53555,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173478,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"H C A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ae7"},"rt":13080,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186670,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ae8"},"rt":61336,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248224,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,K","hovered":"I I I I I O O O O I I O I I O O O O F I 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aea"},"rt":7121,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261254,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aeb"},"rt":34787,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296158,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aec"},"rt":37407,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333669,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B I B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aed"},"rt":22266,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356035,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":"J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aee"},"rt":10159,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366298,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9aef"},"rt":7866,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374270,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9af0"},"rt":5564,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379937,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9af1"},"rt":47583,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427623,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9af2"},"rt":31571,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459297,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"J 03 PM11 AM03 PMG E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9af3"},"rt":22610,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482021,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"X X C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b04"},"rt":25048,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94838,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U F 78101110 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM611 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMA A 10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b05"},"rt":8395,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":103346,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5O E E E Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b06"},"rt":36930,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":140687,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H H A C C C Z Z Z 12 PMC C 12 PM12 PMZ Z C A C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b07"},"rt":49176,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":189965,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMC C F U 04 PMH H H 04 PMH H 03 PM04 PMU 04 PM04 PME E 04 PME E E E D 04 PM04 PM02 PMU U B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b08"},"rt":74351,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":264421,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I J D Z H H O 11 AM11 AMI 12 PMA 03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b0a"},"rt":8577,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":277757,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b0b"},"rt":10968,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288820,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F F Z B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b0c"},"rt":25853,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314785,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F E E G H F F B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b0d"},"rt":12541,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327429,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"3J I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b0e"},"rt":33554,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361082,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O X F B B O 04 PM04 PMX 06 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b0f"},"rt":6204,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367383,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b10"},"rt":5776,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":373490,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b11"},"rt":54624,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":428209,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B Z 04 PMZ Z Z F O Z 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b12"},"rt":20504,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448818,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b13"},"rt":32732,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481648,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X H H O 03 PM02 PMX X X X X K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b24"},"rt":47317,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1810343,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U F 10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMA Z A A 11 AM11 AMA A A 11 AMA C C C C 10 AMC C 10 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b25"},"rt":24295,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1834777,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMU Z B G G K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b26"},"rt":17214,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1852143,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AMC C C 10 AM10 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z 12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b27"},"rt":42336,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1894624,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"A 12 PMC C 03 PM04 PMK H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b28"},"rt":12695,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1907472,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O I I 04 PMI O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b2a"},"rt":14068,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1938072,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"3E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b2b"},"rt":39170,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1977344,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J J J C O N J J 11 AM11 AM11 AMO X X I N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b2c"},"rt":40859,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2018348,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,I,J","hovered":"7L L L B B F 11 AMI G I G F G G F B I E F 03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b2d"},"rt":20977,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2039489,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b2e"},"rt":10209,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2049860,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b2f"},"rt":10481,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2060493,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b30"},"rt":11687,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2072335,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b31"},"rt":29568,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2102010,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM01 PMZ L C M M Z 02 PMZ Z Z 06 PMZ 08 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b32"},"rt":11013,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2113180,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C 12 PM02 PMX 03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b33"},"rt":12037,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2125323,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"403 PM02 PMX X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b44"},"rt":32297,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86840,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM011 AMC A A A A 2A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b45"},"rt":9417,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96429,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z E D E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b46"},"rt":12311,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108935,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b47"},"rt":41633,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":150751,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PMU 04 PMH H A A 604 PM05 PM04 PMU 01 PMU 03 PMZ 04 PMA 12 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b48"},"rt":88689,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239619,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I 10 AMF C 09 AMF F 0U U 03 PMU U 02 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMU O I I I O O 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b4a"},"rt":8075,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":250669,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b4b"},"rt":25605,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276374,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E O O X X H X X B B F F F B B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b4c"},"rt":43607,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320083,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"7B B I I I I J J F F 03 PMC C G G E 02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b4d"},"rt":30438,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":351587,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I G J J I J J J J J I I J B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b4e"},"rt":25496,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377329,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F 02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F F 02 PM02 PMB B F B B B F X X Z C 03 PM04 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b4f"},"rt":7231,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385035,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b50"},"rt":5667,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390866,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b51"},"rt":51143,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442173,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"B J B Z 02 PM02 PM02 PM04 PM02 PMZ 04 PMZ 5Z 04 PMZ Z Z 04 PM04 PM03 PMC O O G X X 01 PM04 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b52"},"rt":31443,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474072,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"F 03 PM03 PM03 PMX 504 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM01 PM12 PME I E E E X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b53"},"rt":84704,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558940,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"004 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMX X X B 02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMX 03 PMM 01 PMO O F G 5O O B B B B 02 PMX O O Z M D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b64"},"rt":108212,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158643,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM01 PM01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b65"},"rt":88452,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":247506,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"10D 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM10 AM06 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AMA 10 AM12 PMA 12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b66"},"rt":29655,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":277641,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"3C 12 PMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b67"},"rt":9684,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":287415,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b68"},"rt":15332,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302840,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b6a"},"rt":7549,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317431,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b6b"},"rt":92158,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409691,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,X","hovered":"F O F C Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b6c"},"rt":111539,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521489,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b6d"},"rt":54132,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":575855,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b6e"},"rt":29119,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":605065,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b6f"},"rt":103018,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":708178,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM12 PMM M M 12 PM02 PMC 01 PM01 PM12 PMM 12 PM10 AMB 01 PM12 PMM M M 01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PMM M 01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PML H H 03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMH H L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b70"},"rt":46236,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":754651,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2F F F B B 12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AMH L L K X X 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b71"},"rt":40103,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":794842,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b72"},"rt":36310,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":831237,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b73"},"rt":9000,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":840326,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b84"},"rt":29253,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64919,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A 6C 11 AM12 PMC A A A O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b85"},"rt":25422,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90465,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5O U H D D E E 04 PME D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b86"},"rt":39812,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130393,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C 10 AMC C 11 AM11 AM12 PMZ 12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b87"},"rt":43076,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173590,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"Z 312 PMC E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b88"},"rt":4809,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178524,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K,U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b8a"},"rt":6155,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":188844,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,I,L","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b8b"},"rt":4723,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193694,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,C,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b8c"},"rt":4444,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198262,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,M,N,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b8d"},"rt":3813,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202201,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b8e"},"rt":7682,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210004,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,I,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b8f"},"rt":4773,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215071,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,K,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b90"},"rt":4567,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219778,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,J,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b91"},"rt":4436,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224700,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,N,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b92"},"rt":4875,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229729,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,H,O,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9b93"},"rt":4853,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234716,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ba4"},"rt":32262,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94229,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"012 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ba5"},"rt":12287,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106707,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4C K D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ba6"},"rt":22471,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129471,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"5A C 10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ba7"},"rt":45810,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":175690,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PMK A C O A A A Z Z U U Z Z H H H K U Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9ba8"},"rt":90569,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":266831,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I A I I I 03 PM02 PM03 PMU U Z Z F F I A A A A I H A A F O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9baa"},"rt":8583,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":278504,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bab"},"rt":29968,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308587,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"G C F F B B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bac"},"rt":32164,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340971,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bad"},"rt":15579,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356660,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bae"},"rt":29431,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386199,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9baf"},"rt":6749,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393245,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bb0"},"rt":8359,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401800,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bb1"},"rt":27207,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":429117,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bb2"},"rt":40222,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469535,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bb3"},"rt":27285,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496934,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bc4"},"rt":52798,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96839,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bc5"},"rt":7035,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":103978,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bc6"},"rt":19668,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123748,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bc7"},"rt":26147,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149999,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"G G G K H U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bc8"},"rt":5335,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155440,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bca"},"rt":8629,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167387,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bcb"},"rt":28613,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196106,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F F F F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bcc"},"rt":31222,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227432,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bcd"},"rt":3865,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231397,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bce"},"rt":34344,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265842,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bcf"},"rt":7833,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273772,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J J M M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bd0"},"rt":7748,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281616,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"8F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bd1"},"rt":35676,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317393,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bd2"},"rt":2094,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319588,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bd3"},"rt":2259,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321954,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9be4"},"rt":127760,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":259288,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMO C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9be5"},"rt":57581,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":317235,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9be6"},"rt":56290,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":373661,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3C C C 10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9be7"},"rt":108084,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":481875,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM01 PMZ Z F A F 01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9be8"},"rt":89046,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":571272,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I A A 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bea"},"rt":20625,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":602928,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9beb"},"rt":26446,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":629510,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bec"},"rt":39403,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":669035,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bed"},"rt":40962,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":710135,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"65"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bee"},"rt":73299,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":783578,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bef"},"rt":19064,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":803015,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bf0"},"rt":17818,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":820968,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bf1"},"rt":39275,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":860374,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bf2"},"rt":35621,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":896153,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PME 03 PM02 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9bf3"},"rt":51600,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":947886,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PME E E 11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c04"},"rt":8485,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":22039,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM12 PM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c05"},"rt":9932,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":32081,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c06"},"rt":12933,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":45134,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c07"},"rt":5826,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":51180,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c08"},"rt":7195,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58473,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c0a"},"rt":9197,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":68446,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c0b"},"rt":17032,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85601,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c0c"},"rt":30081,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115782,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B F F F F F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c0d"},"rt":15669,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":131553,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B M I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c0e"},"rt":13460,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145112,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c0f"},"rt":9895,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155105,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c10"},"rt":6871,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162714,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c11"},"rt":11483,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":174354,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c12"},"rt":6912,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181407,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c13"},"rt":17348,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198890,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"10 AM11 AM02 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c24"},"rt":25377,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137363,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"04 PM12 PM10 AM11 AMF 11 AMF 12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c25"},"rt":13839,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151302,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"5K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c26"},"rt":9341,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":160745,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c27"},"rt":19163,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":180014,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59607cc1f9a239d9c28"},"rt":159153,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":339276,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,A","hovered":"I I 08 AMI I I 08 AM08 AMI I I O O O 08 AM08 AMI A C 08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMA A 08 AMI 08 AMC C A A A 12 PMC 09 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c2a"},"rt":11356,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":353823,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c2b"},"rt":32658,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386595,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C H H C F X X 10 AMX X 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c2c"},"rt":64513,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451213,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B B J J I J F X E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c2d"},"rt":34664,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":486145,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I I I I E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c2e"},"rt":9695,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":495941,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c2f"},"rt":14385,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510437,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"J M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c30"},"rt":11990,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":522543,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c31"},"rt":29554,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":552197,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C Z Z Z Z Z 02 PMZ Z Z Z Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c32"},"rt":8675,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":560978,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c33"},"rt":167096,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":728179,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PMB F M 02 PMC 02 PML C 4F C C J M A M J J M C C 02 PMX X X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c44"},"rt":43676,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117364,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PMO 11 AMC 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c45"},"rt":531518,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":648974,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D 04 PMZ D D D 62408 AMD G G 08 AMO O O 11 AM11 AMO 11 AMC O C C C C H 01 PM09 AM07 PM04 PMA 10 AM08 AMO 03 PM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM05 PM12 PM11 AMA Z 04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMF F F Z Z K K D E U E E 03 PM03 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c46"},"rt":13828,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":663085,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c47"},"rt":9776,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":672960,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c48"},"rt":14441,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":687610,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c4a"},"rt":9447,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":703709,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM66E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c4b"},"rt":37760,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":741563,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I F B B B B M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c4c"},"rt":106617,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":848277,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"5C C B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c4d"},"rt":99241,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":947798,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J J 11 AM10 AMB I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c4e"},"rt":16048,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":964111,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c4f"},"rt":10040,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":974247,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"2M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c50"},"rt":15226,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":989884,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c51"},"rt":25011,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1014990,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C C O B F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c52"},"rt":15979,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1031061,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c53"},"rt":13006,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1044161,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I 02 PM02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c64"},"rt":18938,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127386,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c65"},"rt":11622,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139118,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I X D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c66"},"rt":70777,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210001,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2C C C C C A B 12 PM12 PMZ C C C C U A A 09 AMC A 08 AM09 AMC 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c67"},"rt":16558,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226869,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c68"},"rt":19559,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246535,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"10I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c6a"},"rt":7861,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":260989,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"7E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c6b"},"rt":23287,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284384,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C C F J J O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c6c"},"rt":44705,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329201,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B E F 02 PM01 PM12 PM09 AM9O F B B B I I F G G G O N N Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c6d"},"rt":71484,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":400800,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"9G J I 12 PMB B B B I I I 11 AMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c6e"},"rt":7636,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":408750,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c6f"},"rt":11584,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420451,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"009 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c70"},"rt":8176,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428733,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AM10 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c71"},"rt":10930,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":439769,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"K Z B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c72"},"rt":12752,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452633,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AME 04 PMX X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c73"},"rt":10473,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463783,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c84"},"rt":33291,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100266,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM11 AMA O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c85"},"rt":38578,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138972,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G,B","hovered":"F D J G 04 PMG B B B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c86"},"rt":40442,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":179541,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I,A","hovered":"C 10 AMC A F O F F A F A F A F C C F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c87"},"rt":89255,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268922,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F","hovered":"303 PM04 PMD 04 PM04 PMK F 10 AM10 AMA A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c88"},"rt":88595,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":357836,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U","hovered":"I 12 PMA I I U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c8a"},"rt":41729,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":406143,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I G G M M B G X X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c8b"},"rt":26300,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432576,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 12 PM12 PMF F F G G I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c8c"},"rt":48108,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480812,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c8d"},"rt":116029,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":596969,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4B J J F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c8e"},"rt":50706,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647995,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"10 AM11 AMF F B 05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c8f"},"rt":10887,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":659063,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c90"},"rt":9396,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":668600,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c91"},"rt":24623,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":693344,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"05 PM05 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c92"},"rt":31812,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":725280,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9c93"},"rt":122047,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":847506,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":"12 PM02 PM28C E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ca4"},"rt":12209,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123002,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"6O 11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ca5"},"rt":9317,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132428,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ca6"},"rt":31498,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164057,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C C A A C C A C 10 AMC A C A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ca7"},"rt":18324,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":182492,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"05 PM04 PMZ Z U U G B B B K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ca8"},"rt":51009,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":233604,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K","hovered":"J O I 6A A C C C A C C C A I I I I I I I I I H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9caa"},"rt":5802,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":242035,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cab"},"rt":18116,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260268,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C F F B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cac"},"rt":34326,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294860,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"Z X N C F F F B F J J J E E E E J J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cad"},"rt":14899,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309870,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cae"},"rt":34687,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344669,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"D N F B F F F Z Z X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9caf"},"rt":7466,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352243,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cb0"},"rt":7986,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360347,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cb1"},"rt":34993,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":395446,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O G F J H Z Z Z Z 04 PM04 PMZ Z Z F B B B O O O X B O Z Z F C Z C C C H G E E G F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cb2"},"rt":30479,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426044,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"X 04 PM03 PMO X B B B B O O M M M M M X X J B F F C K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cb3"},"rt":19410,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445563,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K","hovered":"02 PMX X 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cc4"},"rt":27849,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63700,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cc5"},"rt":15546,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":79346,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"H D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cc6"},"rt":24607,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104046,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,A","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cc7"},"rt":41499,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145637,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"03 PM03 PM04 PMA F A A A O O U H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cc8"},"rt":50765,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196496,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cca"},"rt":9370,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":208942,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ccb"},"rt":20350,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229395,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ccc"},"rt":29288,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258776,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ccd"},"rt":12347,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":271228,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cce"},"rt":14106,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285429,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F 04 PMO M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ccf"},"rt":5936,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291462,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cd0"},"rt":4097,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295661,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cd1"},"rt":25732,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":321502,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 2X Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cd2"},"rt":11690,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333287,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cd3"},"rt":23908,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357295,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ce4"},"rt":12223,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58056,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ce5"},"rt":8927,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":67101,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"36"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ce6"},"rt":105131,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172355,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C C C C O O O O J J D D 02 PM03 PMC C A B B A C C C O O J J 11 AM11 AM142C C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ce7"},"rt":11637,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184334,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ce8"},"rt":22027,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206472,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,U","hovered":"I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cea"},"rt":35206,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243395,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G E E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ceb"},"rt":43979,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287506,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cec"},"rt":33377,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321074,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ced"},"rt":13769,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335054,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cee"},"rt":50943,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386107,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F P C G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cef"},"rt":8118,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":394335,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"402 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cf0"},"rt":4886,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399369,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cf1"},"rt":18062,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":417557,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cf2"},"rt":10512,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428178,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9cf3"},"rt":36344,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464632,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,G","hovered":"02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d04"},"rt":102681,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167232,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"11 AMC C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d05"},"rt":124092,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":291558,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"D D D Z 01 PMZ D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d06"},"rt":9595,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":301409,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"1C C 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d07"},"rt":68900,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":370410,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"010 AM11 AM01 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d08"},"rt":133831,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":504485,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d0a"},"rt":9640,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":519640,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d0b"},"rt":14600,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534336,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d0c"},"rt":56580,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591018,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X X 04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d0d"},"rt":19642,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":610759,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d0e"},"rt":97093,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":707945,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d0f"},"rt":6463,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":714672,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d10"},"rt":6799,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":721572,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d11"},"rt":20832,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":742505,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d12"},"rt":24751,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767354,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d13"},"rt":125401,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892861,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d24"},"rt":44615,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":197002,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A 11 AMF F 11 AM08 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d25"},"rt":6395,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203515,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d26"},"rt":10801,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":214428,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d27"},"rt":5628,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":220173,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"06 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d28"},"rt":8565,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":228868,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d2a"},"rt":8559,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243882,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d2b"},"rt":15398,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259392,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d2c"},"rt":41402,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300915,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G G G B B X X F B B B B E X X X X 03 PMO O O O C C C O O C G C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d2d"},"rt":42812,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":343843,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J 09 AMI I I I E I I I I B B B B E E E E E E F B B B B B B B B B B B B B 12 PMJ J J I I 12 PMB J E X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d2e"},"rt":5486,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349452,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F E 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d2f"},"rt":7004,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356568,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d30"},"rt":6748,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363430,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d31"},"rt":7344,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370888,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d32"},"rt":6057,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377057,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d33"},"rt":11713,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388878,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d44"},"rt":18551,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":36977,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d45"},"rt":13907,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50992,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C U Z D 04 PMD D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d46"},"rt":12203,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63308,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"2F C 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d47"},"rt":33581,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97066,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"404 PM03 PMU Z Z Z U U F A O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d48"},"rt":115273,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212464,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM03 PMI 12 PM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d4a"},"rt":11309,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230642,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d4b"},"rt":20559,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251537,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d4c"},"rt":44818,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296492,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B B B E E I 02 PMX E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d4d"},"rt":25879,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":322516,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d4e"},"rt":17799,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340444,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X B B B B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d4f"},"rt":12539,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353149,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d50"},"rt":7741,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361034,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d51"},"rt":28572,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":389736,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B X N M Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d52"},"rt":21524,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411383,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PMX M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d53"},"rt":27162,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438707,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"M 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d64"},"rt":32614,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148606,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"C C C 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMC C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d65"},"rt":23483,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172340,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A D U 01 PMK 05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d66"},"rt":9360,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":181836,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM11 AMC 09 AMC C 11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d67"},"rt":17522,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199474,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z 03 PM04 PMH A H H 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d68"},"rt":19822,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":219441,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I A A 11 AMA A A A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d6a"},"rt":12175,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":238940,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM09 AME G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d6b"},"rt":41897,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280997,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I C C C F 03 PMN X 12 PM01 PMX X O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d6c"},"rt":49557,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330688,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"L B B B B B F G G G C G G G G C C C G B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d6d"},"rt":40185,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370989,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,I","hovered":"M B B B B B B J J J B B 10 AMF 10 AM10 AME B B B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d6e"},"rt":60774,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432003,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d6f"},"rt":8880,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441356,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM12 PMM M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d70"},"rt":6814,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448371,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d71"},"rt":21362,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":470138,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"02 PM02 PM02 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d72"},"rt":19843,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490096,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J 04 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d73"},"rt":77764,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":567973,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I 01 PM02 PMX X X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d84"},"rt":22993,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":279013,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d85"},"rt":11898,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":291013,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d86"},"rt":15506,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":306626,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d87"},"rt":88187,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":394922,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"K 04 PM04 PMF O O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d88"},"rt":117986,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":513333,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"901 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d8a"},"rt":7409,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":529347,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d8b"},"rt":95988,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":625442,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d8c"},"rt":47044,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":672895,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d8d"},"rt":31158,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":704215,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"Z J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d8e"},"rt":35318,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":739635,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d8f"},"rt":26663,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":766400,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d90"},"rt":25349,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":791867,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d91"},"rt":28622,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":820589,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d92"},"rt":45454,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":866143,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMB M O O F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9d93"},"rt":86234,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":952479,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J,M","hovered":"1087612X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9da4"},"rt":13199,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204123,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9da5"},"rt":25034,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":229390,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9da6"},"rt":18935,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248648,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9da7"},"rt":27245,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":276004,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9da8"},"rt":297569,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":573683,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9daa"},"rt":11505,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593768,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dab"},"rt":18329,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":612199,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dac"},"rt":108561,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720868,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dad"},"rt":27818,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":748942,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dae"},"rt":46884,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":795931,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9daf"},"rt":21280,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":817319,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9db0"},"rt":6936,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":824355,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9db1"},"rt":20883,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":845347,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9db2"},"rt":22735,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":868197,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9db3"},"rt":41335,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":909635,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dc4"},"rt":82138,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":207157,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA 61F F Z F F O C C F F F 02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dc5"},"rt":40809,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248208,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D K D D D D D U D K D D K F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dc6"},"rt":11306,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":259598,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"U A C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dc7"},"rt":7963,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":267649,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"O 04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dc8"},"rt":13688,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":281420,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"3J I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dca"},"rt":11714,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":303018,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"986E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dcb"},"rt":28162,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":331267,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"12111096O X X X X X M M B B B Z 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dcc"},"rt":94325,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425678,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"8E E G B G G O X 6C H O X X D C C G B B G C C C C C C C C G F F O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dcd"},"rt":51558,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":477531,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J E E E E J 5F G B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dce"},"rt":9930,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487543,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O O O F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dcf"},"rt":9235,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496861,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM02 PM12 PMM M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dd0"},"rt":13713,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510660,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"X O F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dd1"},"rt":15018,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":525780,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dd2"},"rt":12480,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538394,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C C X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dd3"},"rt":12457,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550943,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9de4"},"rt":12277,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":72682,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9de5"},"rt":15854,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88686,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9de6"},"rt":8077,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96864,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9de7"},"rt":38709,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135676,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"05 PM04 PME 05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9de8"},"rt":17624,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153458,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"7O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dea"},"rt":10354,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167273,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9deb"},"rt":25501,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192880,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dec"},"rt":86297,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279294,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3G C C O B B B B B 12 PM12 PMC B F F B E E 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ded"},"rt":10203,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":289785,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9dee"},"rt":5500,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295390,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9def"},"rt":12747,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308246,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9df0"},"rt":7099,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315516,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9df1"},"rt":40778,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356395,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9df2"},"rt":47272,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403768,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM08 AM001 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9df3"},"rt":36892,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440779,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMX 12 PM12 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e04"},"rt":5266,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":39849,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"2F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e05"},"rt":10249,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50355,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e06"},"rt":22932,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":73483,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,H","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e07"},"rt":16376,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90042,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e08"},"rt":63041,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153251,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e0a"},"rt":8226,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":163829,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"811 AM10 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e0b"},"rt":38871,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202869,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e0c"},"rt":67533,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270569,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e0d"},"rt":27188,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":298188,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e0e"},"rt":6407,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304766,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e0f"},"rt":8062,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312986,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e10"},"rt":6427,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319589,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e11"},"rt":14565,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":334320,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e12"},"rt":8253,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342733,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e13"},"rt":18396,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361288,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e24"},"rt":49501,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130868,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"C J J I 76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e25"},"rt":16053,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":147027,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"O H D D D D G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e26"},"rt":79336,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226466,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"K O C C A C 211 AM12 PM12 PMO O K K C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e27"},"rt":31045,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":257842,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F H H D D G G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e28"},"rt":19523,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":277461,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e2a"},"rt":37917,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":326442,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"3J J J B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e2b"},"rt":22352,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348894,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e2c"},"rt":89623,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438615,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,M","hovered":"6L B B B X X X C B B B X X B B G F B G B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e2d"},"rt":42296,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":481238,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J B B J J B J J B B B J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e2e"},"rt":18980,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500316,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"F F H H 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e2f"},"rt":7436,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":507855,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e30"},"rt":7722,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515677,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e31"},"rt":46092,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561868,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"O Z Z F F F Z Z F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e32"},"rt":38609,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600588,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"G B J I B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e33"},"rt":61519,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":662207,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X X X J I K K M 01 PMM X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e44"},"rt":51425,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125329,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e45"},"rt":14227,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139671,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e46"},"rt":14788,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154849,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e47"},"rt":50671,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206110,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"Z U A C C A A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e48"},"rt":5200,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":211526,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e4a"},"rt":9663,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":226905,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e4b"},"rt":30401,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257425,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e4c"},"rt":64774,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322343,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I B B B 03 PMB M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e4d"},"rt":36414,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359341,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J I J J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e4e"},"rt":11201,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370653,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"2F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e4f"},"rt":9392,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380154,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e50"},"rt":9352,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389619,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e51"},"rt":9725,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399452,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e52"},"rt":9490,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409051,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e53"},"rt":7686,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416854,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e64"},"rt":32054,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100286,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMO 11 AMO 08 AM11 AMC O 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e65"},"rt":57984,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158371,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"D 11 AM10 AM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e66"},"rt":27666,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186138,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I C C A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e67"},"rt":12257,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":198487,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e68"},"rt":101888,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":300469,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"A I K K F F U U U Z U F F F F U U Z F F O O I H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e6a"},"rt":7647,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313480,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e6b"},"rt":15612,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329185,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e6c"},"rt":48520,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377803,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E G G B E J J J X X E E E M E E I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e6d"},"rt":27842,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":405739,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e6e"},"rt":123110,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528941,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F B B F F F F O O F E I I J J J F Z F B B X 03 PMZ Z C G Z Z L A A L Z Z Z M M M B B M M M C C O O X M M M F F X 02 PM04 PM04 PM03 PMX M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e6f"},"rt":6154,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535444,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM12 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e70"},"rt":11017,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":546560,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e71"},"rt":15000,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561654,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e72"},"rt":28074,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":589820,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e73"},"rt":57184,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647088,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M 01 PMX X X M M E B F I 12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX M M M M M M M M M B B B F B F E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e84"},"rt":58116,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133966,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AMA A A 11 AM11 AMA A I I O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e85"},"rt":27799,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161907,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I U A D 04 PM04 PMD J 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e86"},"rt":34157,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196213,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C A A A A F F C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e87"},"rt":11999,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208375,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"J D D D D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e88"},"rt":147706,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":356239,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I I I A A 03 PM03 PMU U Z 01 PM02 PM01 PMZ U U U 02 PM02 PMU C C C 10 AMA A A 12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PMF F 01 PM02 PMO 12 PM01 PM01 PM01 PMU H H Z Z 02 PM03 PM03 PMF H I H I I J H Z 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMD K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e8a"},"rt":11531,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":373381,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e8b"},"rt":28665,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402198,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e8c"},"rt":32144,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":434491,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"98E I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e8d"},"rt":26071,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460712,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e8e"},"rt":89135,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":549991,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"A A F H F F F F F B 12 PMM 02 PMM X 02 PMX 03 PM04 PMX X 4B 04 PMZ Z L L K K A C C C E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e8f"},"rt":8463,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558956,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e90"},"rt":6010,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565089,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e91"},"rt":27993,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593289,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O Z Z F Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e92"},"rt":46103,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":639517,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM02 PMM M X X I I I B 12 PMB B O F Z C X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9e93"},"rt":121401,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":761048,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"502 PMX X X M B B B B F F F F F C C C H H G I I I I B F F X X 02 PMC C J J J M M X X X X H K A A G G E G F F C C O X 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ea4"},"rt":27807,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110060,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA A A C A A A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ea5"},"rt":9079,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119242,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2D D D E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ea6"},"rt":18367,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137714,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 10 AMC C C Z Z 12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ea7"},"rt":32982,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170802,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C A U 5U U F Z O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ea8"},"rt":79107,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":250019,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C I I H H 03 PM03 PM01 PMI I I O O 11 AMO O I O O 01 PM02 PMC U U U U F F Z A O O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eaa"},"rt":11935,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269573,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eab"},"rt":22911,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292594,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eac"},"rt":21136,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313842,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ead"},"rt":31640,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":345586,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eae"},"rt":32490,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378179,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B B B F F B B 02 PMX X X F B B X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eaf"},"rt":7774,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386058,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eb0"},"rt":8581,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":394746,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eb1"},"rt":22492,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":417346,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z O F F F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eb2"},"rt":20549,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438002,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eb3"},"rt":64123,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":502234,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMF F F 02 PMM M M E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ec4"},"rt":20582,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100846,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AMC C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ec5"},"rt":10643,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111586,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F F A A A F K K Z Z K A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ec6"},"rt":16236,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127915,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ec7"},"rt":8803,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136824,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F 04 PM05 PM06 PM06 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ec8"},"rt":14911,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151830,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMZ H A A 11 AMI O O 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eca"},"rt":20388,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180622,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PMJ G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ecb"},"rt":25355,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206077,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C F J B B O O O 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ecc"},"rt":29074,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235245,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PMC E H O G G G B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ecd"},"rt":28301,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":263708,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"H C Z N E F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ece"},"rt":12555,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276370,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F 02 PM02 PMF F X 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ecf"},"rt":15327,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291792,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M 12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMC 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ed0"},"rt":5898,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297795,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"04 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ed1"},"rt":19107,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317019,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X J H Z M J I Z N N 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ed2"},"rt":10538,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327662,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM11 AM10 AM03 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ed3"},"rt":14077,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341846,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ee4"},"rt":33390,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178857,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H A A A A A A 12 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ee5"},"rt":13000,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191956,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ee6"},"rt":20356,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212408,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"5C C C 11 AM12 PM11 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z 11 AM11 AMZ Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ee7"},"rt":39317,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":251821,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"F 02 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM11 AMK G 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ee8"},"rt":94241,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":346160,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"U Z I I I I I O O A A H F 03 PM02 PM01 PMH H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eea"},"rt":5745,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359156,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eeb"},"rt":18071,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377323,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"9J F X B F F 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eec"},"rt":49623,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427040,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E E E E E E E F F F F E E F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eed"},"rt":28141,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":455289,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"11J I 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eee"},"rt":21331,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476723,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PMZ M B B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9eef"},"rt":9068,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":485889,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"N X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ef0"},"rt":5286,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491272,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ef1"},"rt":26290,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":517656,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H 04 PM04 PM03 PM11 AM11 AM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ef2"},"rt":21622,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":539373,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F 03 PM02 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ef3"},"rt":26116,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565589,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M 02 PM02 PM02 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f04"},"rt":42755,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":70291,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f05"},"rt":12496,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":82948,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"05 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMH K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f06"},"rt":77993,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161059,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,H","hovered":"C F A 10 AMC C C A A A A A A A A A H H H C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f07"},"rt":66255,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227614,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f08"},"rt":18102,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246047,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O O I A A 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f0a"},"rt":20432,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269137,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,I,O","hovered":"10 AM11 AM10 AM09 AMJ I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f0b"},"rt":40760,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310003,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f0c"},"rt":92466,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402613,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B B B B B B X X F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f0d"},"rt":60047,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":462995,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2J M B B J J J B 11 AM10 AM08 AMI J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f0e"},"rt":14065,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477671,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f0f"},"rt":8951,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486723,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f10"},"rt":5491,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":492311,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"4F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f11"},"rt":12533,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":504945,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"O 01 PMZ Z Z N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f12"},"rt":10816,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515857,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f13"},"rt":18616,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534591,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PMZ 02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f24"},"rt":19290,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58353,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f25"},"rt":17499,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75944,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"D D K D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f26"},"rt":24596,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100629,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I C C C C C 4A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f27"},"rt":11415,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":112130,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f28"},"rt":14261,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":126477,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f2a"},"rt":26639,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":161262,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f2b"},"rt":14552,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175907,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f2c"},"rt":27091,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203089,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f2d"},"rt":13931,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":217119,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f2e"},"rt":9695,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226909,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f2f"},"rt":7717,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234715,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f30"},"rt":3430,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238232,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f31"},"rt":36338,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":274661,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f32"},"rt":17978,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292725,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f33"},"rt":28874,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321685,"subject":"TCS5Z","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42258","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f44"},"rt":155626,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1052919,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM210 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM409 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMF D D 12 PM09 AM09 AMC C 11 AM01 PMZ Z Z Z Z 10 AM10 AM11 AMK Z Z 01 PMZ Z Z F F F F A 10 AMA A A I D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f45"},"rt":24444,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1077734,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D D 11 AM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f46"},"rt":224905,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1302798,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F","hovered":"C C 10 AMC C C U 01 PMZ A A C C C C C 10 AM10 AMC C 11 AM08 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AMU U 01 PM01 PMF F 01 PM12 PMC C C C 11 AMI C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f47"},"rt":75713,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1379047,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"6504 PMD D D D D D 02 PM01 PM01 PMU U 11 AM10 AM09 AMO C O O O 09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f48"},"rt":43885,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1423295,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM08 AM08 AMO A I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f4a"},"rt":10841,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1444892,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f4b"},"rt":88282,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1533361,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM08 AMF Z Z 03 PM02 PMF 11 AM11 AMF F F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f4c"},"rt":168652,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1702843,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B F 10 AMJ X X X 09 AMX B M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f4d"},"rt":43204,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1746644,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O J J J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f4e"},"rt":5967,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1752851,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f4f"},"rt":10397,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1763456,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f50"},"rt":9561,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1773196,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f51"},"rt":40271,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1813695,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f52"},"rt":33597,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1847492,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f53"},"rt":126589,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1974259,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f64"},"rt":19872,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76035,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"111 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f65"},"rt":9106,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85225,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f66"},"rt":23790,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109097,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f67"},"rt":16008,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125209,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f68"},"rt":37674,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162969,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"I U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f6a"},"rt":9108,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":176841,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AMI E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f6b"},"rt":42330,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219402,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,J","hovered":"3C J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f6c"},"rt":20028,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239665,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f6d"},"rt":9599,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":249496,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f6e"},"rt":18115,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267841,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f6f"},"rt":15989,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283914,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMJ J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f70"},"rt":4155,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288153,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f71"},"rt":22131,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":310369,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"Z Z Z B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f72"},"rt":22821,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333273,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3B B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f73"},"rt":26829,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360185,"subject":"6M284","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35848","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"2X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f84"},"rt":54658,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88184,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f85"},"rt":27737,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116034,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"04 PM04 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f86"},"rt":62508,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178658,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f87"},"rt":71189,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":250190,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PM04 PM12 PM12 PM02 PM01 PMZ Z 02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f88"},"rt":124894,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":375389,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PMZ K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f8a"},"rt":10354,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":389484,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f8b"},"rt":35983,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425584,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f8c"},"rt":20592,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446294,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f8d"},"rt":16981,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":463387,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f8e"},"rt":47120,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510633,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PM09 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f8f"},"rt":10039,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":520786,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f90"},"rt":7804,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528707,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f91"},"rt":28823,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":557652,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"08 AM11 AMM X 06 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f92"},"rt":44238,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":602001,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM01 PM03 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9f93"},"rt":32799,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":634912,"subject":"JMZMZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42657","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"4J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fa4"},"rt":45369,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172999,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM02 PMU O I 11 AMF F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fa5"},"rt":23502,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":197115,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fa6"},"rt":15518,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212767,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMC 11 AM11 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fa7"},"rt":17379,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":230374,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fa8"},"rt":43771,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":274275,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AMC I I I A A A A A I 5I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9faa"},"rt":23514,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":308526,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E 766G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fab"},"rt":50387,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359050,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I I C O O X X X X O O O X O X X O F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fac"},"rt":38442,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397948,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C B 4B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fad"},"rt":80667,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":478776,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B X J J I E B B B B J J I J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fae"},"rt":18095,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":497947,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AM09 AMX F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9faf"},"rt":13039,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":511410,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMM L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fb0"},"rt":15838,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":527371,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PMF 10 AM10 AMF G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fb1"},"rt":21213,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":549031,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AMZ 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fb2"},"rt":12837,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562002,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fb3"},"rt":18124,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580821,"subject":"H0HHM","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM02 PMX K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fc4"},"rt":72598,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162067,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"11 AM11 AM6510 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM508 AM09 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM1008 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fc5"},"rt":60563,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":222976,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"12 PM12 PMZ 04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM12 PM11 AM10 AMO 11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMX J 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fc6"},"rt":140175,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":363481,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"501 PM12 PMC 10 AM10 AM10 AMC C C C C C C 10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM10 AMC 12 PM12 PM01 PMZ Z F 04 PM03 PM05 PM04 PMC 0C C C 10 AMC 12 PM12 PM12 PMA A Z Z Z Z Z U B B B B G G D D D E 111 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fc7"},"rt":41160,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":404974,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"304 PM7A F 04 PM05 PMG G 05 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PMH H Z Z 12 PM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fc8"},"rt":17427,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":422499,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H I I 11 AMI I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fca"},"rt":11609,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":440686,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fcb"},"rt":28587,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469371,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B B B B B B B B B B B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fcc"},"rt":36418,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":505880,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B B X X B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fcd"},"rt":22577,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":528545,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fce"},"rt":8395,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":537032,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fcf"},"rt":6774,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543900,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6M 12 PM12 PMF 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fd0"},"rt":5754,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":549750,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fd1"},"rt":33583,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":583429,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 04 PM04 PMZ O O 03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMX 01 PMM 12 PMB B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fd2"},"rt":26357,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":609878,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"6J J 12 PM11 AM10 AM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fd3"},"rt":93771,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":703740,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"07 PM05 PM04 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMM M 01 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM02 PMM M M M 02 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM10 AMJ 11 AM10 AM408 AM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM33"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fe4"},"rt":305939,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1584521,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5411 AM11 AM11 AM08 AM09 AM02 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM02 PMA 11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM5611 AM10 AM10 AM10 AMC 11 AM03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM11 AM12 PM01 PME 11 AM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM05 PM04 PM12 PM11 AM01 PMC C C J X Z Z 01 PM01 PMZ U U U F 04 PM05 PM06 PM05 PM05 PMG B E E E B B 05 PM04 PM04 PMJ J J K K J J H B B G G K U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fe5"},"rt":142969,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1727805,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"H D D 04 PMA F F 01 PM12 PM12 PMA O Z 01 PMZ Z U U U H Z 01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMU F F H F H H Z 01 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM05 PM05 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fe6"},"rt":206463,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1934583,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"C U C C 10 AM12 PMA O O A A Z Z F F F F H H H H Z Z 01 PM10 AMA O O I I 11 AM11 AMZ Z 01 PMU H H H H H J X K G G G D D 04 PMB B E E B 312 PM12 PM12 PMH Z Z 8B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fe7"},"rt":15379,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1950270,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"A 04 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fe8"},"rt":252681,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":2203060,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I 11 AMO 11 AMJ H H H J H H Z Z 01 PMF Z A K 03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PMD E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fea"},"rt":20495,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2230973,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9feb"},"rt":22266,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2253342,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F B F B B B B B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fec"},"rt":38367,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2291816,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"G L L H B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fed"},"rt":21516,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2313441,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fee"},"rt":99489,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2413033,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B F B B 12 PMI I B B M G 01 PMX X X O 03 PMH H O O 02 PMX X C C G C C 11 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9fef"},"rt":10353,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2423792,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ff0"},"rt":5442,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2429338,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ff1"},"rt":45155,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2474595,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PMZ Z Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ff2"},"rt":32041,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2506745,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X 02 PM01 PM02 PMM M M X X X O O O C C C 01 PM12 PMB B F 1E 10 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239d9ff3"},"rt":65201,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2572055,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMB B F E 02 PM02 PMM M M M B B B 12 PM12 PMB G 12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da004"},"rt":12021,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":34755,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da005"},"rt":10898,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":45771,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da006"},"rt":12992,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58871,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da007"},"rt":7031,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66017,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"Z U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da008"},"rt":8023,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":74148,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da00a"},"rt":8146,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":85010,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da00b"},"rt":16533,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101661,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C B B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da00c"},"rt":20764,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122544,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B I F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da00d"},"rt":9655,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":132392,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da00e"},"rt":8780,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141715,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da00f"},"rt":5755,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147665,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da010"},"rt":8327,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156183,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da011"},"rt":13987,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":170277,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da012"},"rt":20372,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190759,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da013"},"rt":3487,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194356,"subject":"NV8XN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28664","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da024"},"rt":24993,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137425,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da025"},"rt":23145,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":160668,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da026"},"rt":30946,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191709,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da027"},"rt":12360,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204164,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da028"},"rt":50766,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":255024,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,D","hovered":"I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da02a"},"rt":18541,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":281798,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da02b"},"rt":21875,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303769,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da02c"},"rt":28398,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332264,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A E E L E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da02d"},"rt":52830,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":385191,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da02e"},"rt":11018,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396308,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da02f"},"rt":9691,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406094,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da030"},"rt":48716,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454903,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"J J J J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da031"},"rt":60729,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":515728,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G","hovered":"Z J J J J J O Z Z Z Z F Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da032"},"rt":27112,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543320,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"09 AM02 PM04 PM03 PM03 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da033"},"rt":39805,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583225,"subject":"EBSJV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41165","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"M X J B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da044"},"rt":31594,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58372,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O 12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMH X X F 11 AMF U U U U F C F F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da045"},"rt":10698,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":69174,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D D Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da046"},"rt":9592,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78871,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4K C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da047"},"rt":7184,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86150,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F F 04 PM05 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da048"},"rt":10362,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96608,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da04a"},"rt":45557,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":147200,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6I I 08 AM09 AM10 AM008 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMF X X G G G 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PMO E 02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM06 PMN H 04 PMC 11 AMC C C C G C O C G B 10 AMF G 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da04b"},"rt":15821,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163122,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"08 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da04c"},"rt":43838,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207056,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G G G E E F 03 PM04 PM04 PMO F O O O X O C G F 10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da04d"},"rt":23556,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230714,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"F B B B I I I B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da04e"},"rt":10914,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241733,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7C 02 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da04f"},"rt":6698,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248535,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMH G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da050"},"rt":4624,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253258,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da051"},"rt":8295,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261661,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da052"},"rt":5442,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267208,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PMM X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da053"},"rt":8747,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276060,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"M M 12 PM01 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da064"},"rt":75904,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199794,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I 11 AM01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA I I X X A 11 AM11 AMA A C C A C C A A F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da065"},"rt":23933,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":224029,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"9D D D E E E E D J H D D E G B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da066"},"rt":30067,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":254204,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"5A C C C C C A A Z C C A C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da067"},"rt":110425,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":364765,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A C E E E E E E X X X C A A A C C A U B B K X X Z Z F 06 PM05 PM04 PME E 12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da068"},"rt":50219,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":415264,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I 3C 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da06a"},"rt":23788,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":444540,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E E 1066E E E E E G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da06b"},"rt":29465,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474090,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F F B 5J B B F M X O O H Z Z D C C X O Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da06c"},"rt":51014,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525199,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A C B B B B F F E G E 7C F B B B B F F E F F J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da06d"},"rt":19064,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":544375,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"3F J J J J J J I B B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da06e"},"rt":55624,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600084,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da06f"},"rt":10562,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":610735,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da070"},"rt":8967,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619796,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da071"},"rt":22622,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":642544,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"3B O Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da072"},"rt":37029,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679677,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C C B G O 4B 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da073"},"rt":43453,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":723273,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"2C X X 5H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da084"},"rt":15473,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":81040,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da085"},"rt":8350,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89469,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da086"},"rt":10391,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99941,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C C C 10 AM11 AM12 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da087"},"rt":25412,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125432,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PMC C C 311 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da088"},"rt":13965,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139477,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"4A I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da08a"},"rt":9535,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":153705,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5I B B 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da08b"},"rt":11683,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165466,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"4I B O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da08c"},"rt":17090,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182632,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"8E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da08d"},"rt":21688,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":204399,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da08e"},"rt":6544,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211023,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da08f"},"rt":15240,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226342,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"J 12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da090"},"rt":7356,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233777,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"5F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da091"},"rt":9630,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243483,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da092"},"rt":6652,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250214,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"5J 03 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da093"},"rt":11435,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261725,"subject":"43L8M","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0a4"},"rt":150903,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208410,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0a5"},"rt":33246,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":242087,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0a6"},"rt":24269,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":266709,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0a7"},"rt":18661,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":285787,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0a8"},"rt":50705,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":336874,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0aa"},"rt":12555,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":361696,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ab"},"rt":36197,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398240,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ac"},"rt":278084,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":676683,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ad"},"rt":165488,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":842518,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ae"},"rt":23681,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":866599,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0af"},"rt":12073,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":878958,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0b0"},"rt":12285,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":891455,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0b1"},"rt":36883,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":928548,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0b2"},"rt":10403,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":939136,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0b3"},"rt":39017,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":978297,"subject":"23WXV","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43089","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0c4"},"rt":22324,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":189656,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0c5"},"rt":17010,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206784,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"A Z U 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0c6"},"rt":25125,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":232034,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"A C C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0c7"},"rt":73537,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":305751,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"K K 01 PM01 PMU H H 01 PMI 11 AMA A O A A F F 01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0c8"},"rt":86557,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":392585,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H I A A 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ca"},"rt":9275,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414436,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0cb"},"rt":22282,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436818,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0cc"},"rt":38938,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":475850,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0cd"},"rt":32700,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":508651,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ce"},"rt":33848,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542600,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0cf"},"rt":11105,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553801,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0d0"},"rt":5395,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559301,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0d1"},"rt":22632,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":582035,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0d2"},"rt":46547,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":628684,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0d3"},"rt":40533,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":669318,"subject":"34FAZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32667","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0e4"},"rt":31048,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203072,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0e5"},"rt":32468,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":235763,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0e6"},"rt":10884,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246795,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0e7"},"rt":16003,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":263028,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0e8"},"rt":70792,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":342660,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ea"},"rt":18109,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":373675,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0eb"},"rt":21658,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395598,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ec"},"rt":84656,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480400,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ed"},"rt":27203,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":508028,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ee"},"rt":18883,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":527116,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0ef"},"rt":11905,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":539458,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0f0"},"rt":9860,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":549455,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0f1"},"rt":305979,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":855531,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"A 1208 AM11 AMM M M 01 PM01 PM03 PM03 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0f2"},"rt":21231,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":879304,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da0f3"},"rt":25075,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":905666,"subject":"JHTYA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da104"},"rt":27942,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":205466,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F 11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da105"},"rt":13529,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":219078,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da106"},"rt":13498,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":232655,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da107"},"rt":11644,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":244402,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da108"},"rt":23588,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268068,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da10a"},"rt":12288,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":286554,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da10b"},"rt":20409,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307041,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F C C H X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da10c"},"rt":47233,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354352,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G X B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da10d"},"rt":22445,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":376874,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"7J B J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da10e"},"rt":7955,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":384908,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da10f"},"rt":10969,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395954,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da110"},"rt":7949,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403980,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"9F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da111"},"rt":10294,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414351,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da112"},"rt":8191,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":422627,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"9X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da113"},"rt":21195,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443899,"subject":"S6C3N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"108G X 02 PMX X X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da124"},"rt":18271,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":198361,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da125"},"rt":11170,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":209757,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da126"},"rt":29245,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239130,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C J U O A A C A A A A A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da127"},"rt":368,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239624,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da128"},"rt":91534,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":331273,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"403 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da12a"},"rt":7936,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":345089,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da12b"},"rt":22482,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367689,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da12c"},"rt":32976,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":400785,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da12d"},"rt":32317,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":433226,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da12e"},"rt":34906,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468257,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da12f"},"rt":8405,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476781,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da130"},"rt":7854,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":484751,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da131"},"rt":28569,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":513451,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da132"},"rt":31924,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":545511,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da133"},"rt":57642,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603270,"subject":"853JQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da144"},"rt":18792,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120559,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da145"},"rt":14545,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135203,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da146"},"rt":17635,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152936,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"08 AM09 AMC A Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da147"},"rt":73150,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226183,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM112 PM01 PM12 PMO I I H H H H 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da148"},"rt":44198,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":270696,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"G I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da14a"},"rt":7959,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":329018,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da14b"},"rt":28300,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357416,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da14c"},"rt":81882,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439396,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E,I,J,N","hovered":"B J X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da14d"},"rt":52647,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":492383,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"G J J X M 01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da14e"},"rt":175176,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":667659,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da14f"},"rt":10834,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678779,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da150"},"rt":10193,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":689075,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da151"},"rt":18794,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":707969,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da152"},"rt":69529,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":777595,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMO O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da153"},"rt":2680,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":780594,"subject":"A3QHP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37925","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da164"},"rt":9020,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":30167,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da165"},"rt":13309,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":43552,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da166"},"rt":18985,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":62613,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O H K A 11 AM011 AMC C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da167"},"rt":25243,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":87937,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da168"},"rt":21529,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109541,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da16a"},"rt":23096,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":134456,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"B 10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da16b"},"rt":3326,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137865,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da16c"},"rt":1702,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":139642,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da16d"},"rt":3787,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":143504,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da16e"},"rt":19632,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163214,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,J","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da16f"},"rt":2578,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165868,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da170"},"rt":1603,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167546,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da171"},"rt":1604,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":169224,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da172"},"rt":2081,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171379,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da173"},"rt":1884,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173338,"subject":"31E2K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37082","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da184"},"rt":20426,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52425,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A C A Z Z Z F F F 10 AM11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da185"},"rt":6772,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":59303,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da186"},"rt":6146,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":65561,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da187"},"rt":10587,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76419,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"B 04 PMK C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da188"},"rt":19430,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":95965,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I O O A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da18a"},"rt":15507,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":115447,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"08 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da18b"},"rt":3234,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118788,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da18c"},"rt":2067,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120963,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da18d"},"rt":4139,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":125215,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da18e"},"rt":3028,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128356,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da18f"},"rt":3543,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132005,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da190"},"rt":5488,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137599,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da191"},"rt":10483,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":148192,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da192"},"rt":8249,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156547,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da193"},"rt":10655,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167310,"subject":"6W8J7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33597","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1a4"},"rt":12432,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":61025,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1a5"},"rt":8785,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":69900,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1a6"},"rt":5899,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75875,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1a7"},"rt":9959,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85915,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"12 PM01 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1a8"},"rt":11513,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97513,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1aa"},"rt":19226,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":138342,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ab"},"rt":20526,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158953,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ac"},"rt":57622,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216657,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ad"},"rt":33451,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":250192,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ae"},"rt":41218,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291492,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1af"},"rt":9770,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301370,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1b0"},"rt":113608,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415060,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1b1"},"rt":133731,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":549022,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1b2"},"rt":61743,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":611001,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM603 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1b3"},"rt":33525,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":644758,"subject":"EBSH0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1c4"},"rt":14898,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":59708,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"6K 06 PM04 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1c5"},"rt":6591,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66408,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1c6"},"rt":12381,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78902,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1c7"},"rt":17378,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96382,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E,G,B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1c8"},"rt":9204,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105697,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ca"},"rt":12077,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":120238,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1cb"},"rt":4025,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124365,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1cc"},"rt":3625,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128098,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1cd"},"rt":16210,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":144410,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ce"},"rt":11613,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156126,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1cf"},"rt":10851,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167080,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1d0"},"rt":4543,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171725,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1d1"},"rt":13702,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":185529,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"Z Z Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1d2"},"rt":7145,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192779,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1d3"},"rt":10699,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203580,"subject":"DMJ14","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35743","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1e4"},"rt":42008,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":91902,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"508 AM09 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMF F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1e5"},"rt":8873,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100877,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"B B D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1e6"},"rt":10296,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111276,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1e7"},"rt":5089,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116470,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1e8"},"rt":56565,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173144,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,D","hovered":"I I I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ea"},"rt":9041,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":185707,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1eb"},"rt":40820,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226623,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,J,N,X","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ec"},"rt":29338,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256061,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ed"},"rt":19345,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275512,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ee"},"rt":7999,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283613,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1ef"},"rt":12927,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296638,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1f0"},"rt":7815,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304554,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1f1"},"rt":48311,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352966,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F O Z Z 02 PM02 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1f2"},"rt":18081,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371147,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":"J J O Z Z 03 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da1f3"},"rt":40822,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412073,"subject":"05EWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37220","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"J M 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM10"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da204"},"rt":10007,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52404,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da205"},"rt":14700,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":67178,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4E E 04 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da206"},"rt":12953,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":80209,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z C 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da207"},"rt":9317,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89603,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"03 PM05 PM04 PMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da208"},"rt":25412,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115091,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"U I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da20a"},"rt":12034,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":128889,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM08 AMM M 10 AM09 AM09 AM08 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da20b"},"rt":1230,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130197,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da20c"},"rt":13820,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144095,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da20d"},"rt":592,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":144763,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da20e"},"rt":508,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145358,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da20f"},"rt":1735,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147169,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da210"},"rt":1461,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148706,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da211"},"rt":1451,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":150236,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da212"},"rt":1255,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151564,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da213"},"rt":1567,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153208,"subject":"48H7W","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30018","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da224"},"rt":108269,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210380,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM008 AM09 AM11 AMF F C C J C 11 AMF 11 AMC 11 AM08 AM10 AM09 AM11 AMC C F 11 AM11 AMO O 11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da225"},"rt":17081,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227717,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMD D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da226"},"rt":72924,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":300732,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"2C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da227"},"rt":16339,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":317336,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"05 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da228"},"rt":19931,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":337353,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da22a"},"rt":11599,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":371298,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da22b"},"rt":29667,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401338,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F F F F B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da22c"},"rt":65662,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467093,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMG F G E G G G G G G G I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da22d"},"rt":33215,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":500698,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I 212 PMZ B 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da22e"},"rt":175085,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":675877,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B F B 09 AM10 AMF F Z X B B 12 PMO F F F B F 03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMF B O 03 PM10 AMO O 04 PM04 PMZ 04 PMF F F Z Z Z M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da22f"},"rt":9039,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":685165,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da230"},"rt":10387,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":695640,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da231"},"rt":14312,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":710050,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da232"},"rt":38842,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":748981,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PMI O 03 PMM M M M X X X 02 PMX X X X E E E F M 01 PM12 PM02 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da233"},"rt":109338,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":858413,"subject":"TAEHJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"11 AM01 PM02 PMP K A I E 11 AM11 AME E E E 11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMF F F B B 12 PMB B F F F 12 PMM M X B B F F F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da244"},"rt":350456,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1297107,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"111 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMZ A A A A A Z I I A A F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da245"},"rt":117173,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1414592,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,A,K","hovered":"G G K 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da246"},"rt":80151,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1495103,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U,B,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da247"},"rt":38186,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1533593,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,H,K","hovered":"K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da248"},"rt":93191,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1626874,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I A A A A I F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da24a"},"rt":36125,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1672596,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,I,O","hovered":"11C I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da24b"},"rt":311341,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1984022,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,O","hovered":"E J X N D D N 05 PMD C H F F Z Z M X O O O M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da24c"},"rt":284866,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2269223,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G,I,J,O","hovered":"11L G B B B 12 PMB X X X X C C G E G G C C 03 PM04 PM03 PMX X X B B E E E E E L F B B 12 PMF F K L H H C C C M M X X B B X X B J X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da24d"},"rt":37292,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2306840,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da24e"},"rt":22842,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2329784,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da24f"},"rt":61620,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2391486,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,X","hovered":"08 AMM 12 PMM M M X X X X O O Z M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da250"},"rt":24298,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2416088,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,J","hovered":"B B B B F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da251"},"rt":17068,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2433244,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da252"},"rt":41681,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2475014,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,O,X","hovered":"O O X X 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da253"},"rt":9751,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2484849,"subject":"X2NQN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30042","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da264"},"rt":23117,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":141573,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da265"},"rt":11221,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152897,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da266"},"rt":36827,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":189819,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da267"},"rt":11311,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":201230,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da268"},"rt":21532,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":222872,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da26a"},"rt":13347,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":244326,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da26b"},"rt":22480,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266905,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da26c"},"rt":55031,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322032,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da26d"},"rt":47742,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":369875,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I I E E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da26e"},"rt":63374,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":433347,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM05 PMF F F G G G F F F Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da26f"},"rt":10353,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443987,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da270"},"rt":12171,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456258,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"A F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da271"},"rt":34369,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490732,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z N Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da272"},"rt":136363,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":627192,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"G 01 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMX G 01 PME E F F B B X 02 PMF M N Z Z H O O O O O X X B 12 PMM M F F F F F E J E 11 AMJ G A A G G 03 PMX 03 PMO O O O B I I I F F F F C C 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da273"},"rt":87987,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":715461,"subject":"RDYS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da284"},"rt":17750,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64314,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da285"},"rt":11440,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75849,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da286"},"rt":16147,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92090,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C C C Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da287"},"rt":49681,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":141906,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMC A Z Z O O O H H H H U U U U U K J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da288"},"rt":64707,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206706,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z I O O O I O I O O O I 03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMH I U A A U 01 PMF U F F Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da28a"},"rt":8008,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":219358,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da28b"},"rt":14228,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233677,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B F F B J B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da28c"},"rt":43360,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277131,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5M J J J E X E X B F F E 01 PM02 PMX 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da28d"},"rt":22047,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299270,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X K J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da28e"},"rt":27420,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326784,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da28f"},"rt":17370,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344244,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da290"},"rt":8705,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353043,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da291"},"rt":32105,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":385241,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"X X M M M X B 12 PMB 04 PM04 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da292"},"rt":53469,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438807,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PM12 PMM O 11 AMB B M G 12 PM01 PM04 PMN 04 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"624fc59707cc1f9a239da293"},"rt":37317,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476219,"subject":"19SNU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31040","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM02 PM02 PM12 PME E E G C B C J J B B "}]
